The Island on Bird Street is a drama, war film directed by Søren Kragh-Jacobsen.
Alex is an 11-year old boy who, during WWII, hides in the Jewish ghetto from Nazis
after all his relatives have been sent to the concentration camp.
The movie portrays the ghetto through his eyes.
Stefan, played by Patrick Bergin.
Alex, played by Jordan Kiziuk.
Boruch, played by Jack Warden.
Doctor Studjinsky, played by James Bolam.
Bolek, played by Michael Byrne.
Goehler, played by Stefan Sauk.
The Island on Bird Street (Danish: Øen i Fuglegaden) is a 1997 Danish
produced drama film directed by Søren Kragh-Jacobsen.
It is based on the novel The Island on Bird Street.
The film explores themes of nazi, jewish ghetto, world
war ii, based on true story, orphan.
The tone is emotional.